Faculty of Arts fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Faculty Members, 1965 - 1979; F-2-2; 58 cm of textual records
  - Subject files, 1965 - 1979; F-2-2-1; 18 cm of textual records
    - Staffing appointments, 1974 - 1976; F-2-2-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-15)
    - Staffing appointments, 1973 - 1976; F-2-2-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-15)
    - Staffing appointments, 1973 - 1976; F-2-2-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-15)
    - Staffing appointments, 1973 - 1976; F-2-2-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-15)
  - Department of English, 1974 - 1975; F-2-2-2; 2 cm of textual records
    Department of English
    - Department of English Search Committee, 1974 - 1975; F-2-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-15)
  - Department of Economics and Commerce, 1977 - 1978; F-2-2-3; 2 cm of textual records
    Department of Economics
    - Department of Economics and Commerce, 1977 - 1978; F-2-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-15)
  - Department of History, 1971 - 1974; F-2-2-4; 3 cm of textual records
    Department of History
    - Department of History Search Committee, 1973 - 1974; F-2-2-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-16)
    - Department of History Correspondence, 1971; F-2-2-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-16)
  - Department of Modern Languages, 1966 - 1978; F-2-2-5; 21 cm of textual records
    Department of Languages, Literature and Linguistics
    - Tenure, 1974 - 1978; F-2-2-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-16)
    - Faculty - H., 1969 - 1970; F-2-2-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-16)
    - Faculty - H., 1973 - 1976; F-2-2-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-16)
    - Faculty - H., 1977 - 1978; F-2-2-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-16)
    - Staffing appointments, 1974 - 1976; F-2-2-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-16)
    - Faculty - A, 1971; F-2-2-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-16)
    - Faculty - B, 1968 - 1974; F-2-2-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-16)
    - Faculty - B, 1966 - 1967; F-2-2-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - B, 1966 - 1970; F-2-2-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - D, 1968; F-2-2-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - D, 1967; F-2-2-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - D, 1968 - 1970; F-2-2-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - D, 1967; F-2-2-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - E, 1967 - 1968; F-2-2-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - F, 1967 - 1970; F-2-2-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - G, 1968 - 1976; F-2-2-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - G, 1968 - 1974; F-2-2-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - H, 1969; F-2-2-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - H, 1969 - 1970; F-2-2-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - H, 1967 - 1972; F-2-2-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - H, 1977 - 1978; F-2-2-5-0-21 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - M, 1968 - 1974; F-2-2-5-0-22 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - M, 1967 - 1970; F-2-2-5-0-23 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - N, 1967 - 1970; F-2-2-5-0-24 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - O, 1968; F-2-2-5-0-25 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - S, 1967 - 1975; F-2-2-5-0-26 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - V, 1974 - 1978; F-2-2-5-0-27 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - V, 1970 - 1975; F-2-2-5-0-28 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - W, 1967 - 1971; F-2-2-5-0-29 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
    - Faculty - W, 1970 - 1974; F-2-2-5-0-30 (Archival box - standard 2-17)
  - Department of Psychology, 1966 - 1977; F-2-2-6; 10 cm of textual records
    Department of Psychology
    - Deptartment of Psychology - appointments, 1969; F-2-2-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
    - External review, 1973; F-2-2-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
    - External review, 1973; F-2-2-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
    - Search Committee minutes, 1966 - 1974; F-2-2-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
    - Search Committee minutes, 1975 - 1977; F-2-2-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
    - Investigations, F-2-2-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
    - Faculty - A, 1970 - 1971; F-2-2-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
    - Faculty - D, 1970 - 1971; F-2-2-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
    - Faculty - D, 1972 - 1973; F-2-2-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
    - Faculty - M, 1970; F-2-2-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
  - Department of Philosophy, 1966 - 1974; F-2-2-7; 2 cm of textual records
    Department of Philosophy
    - Search Committee minutes, 1966 - 1973; F-2-2-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
    - Faculty - R, 1974; F-2-2-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-18)
- Faculty Committees, 1965 - 1984; F-2-3; 2.65 m of textual records
  Series consists of the records of various faculty committees. It includes circulars, correspondence, minutes of meetings, and memoranda.
  - Dean's Advisory Committee, 1966 - 1984; F-2-3-1; 59 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Arts. Dean's Advisory Committee
    - Agenda and minutes, 1966; F-2-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-19)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1967; F-2-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-19)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1968; F-2-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-19)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1969; F-2-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-19)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1969; F-2-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-19)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1970; F-2-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-19)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1970; F-2-3-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-19)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1970; F-2-3-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-20)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1970; F-2-3-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-20)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1971; F-2-3-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-20)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1971; F-2-3-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 2-20)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1971; F-2-3-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 2-20)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1971; F-2-3-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 2-20)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1972; F-2-3-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 2-20)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1972; F-2-3-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 2-21)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1972; F-2-3-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 2-21)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1973; F-2-3-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 2-21)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1973; F-2-3-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 2-21)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1974; F-2-3-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 2-21)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1974; F-2-3-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 2-21)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1970 - 1974; F-2-3-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 2-21)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1975; F-2-3-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 2-21)
    - Papers, 1975; F-2-3-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 2-22)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1975; F-2-3-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 2-22)
    - Papers, 1975; F-2-3-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 2-22)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1976; F-2-3-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 2-22)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1976; F-2-3-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 2-22)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1977; F-2-3-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 2-22)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1977; F-2-3-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 2-22)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1977; F-2-3-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 2-22)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1978; F-2-3-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 2-22)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1978; F-2-3-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 2-23)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1979; F-2-3-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 2-23)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1979; F-2-3-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 2-23)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1980; F-2-3-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 2-23)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1980; F-2-3-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 2-23)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1981 - 1984; F-2-3-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 2-23)
  - Faculty of Arts meetings, 1965 - 1979; F-2-3-2; 24 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Arts. Faculty Meeting
    - Terms of reference, 1966 - 1969; F-2-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-23)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1965 - 1966; F-2-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-23)
    - Memoranda and papers, 1966; F-2-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-23)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1967; F-2-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - Memoranda and papers, 1967; F-2-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1968; F-2-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - Memoranda and papers, 1968; F-2-3-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - Memoranda and papers, 1969; F-2-3-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1969 - 1970; F-2-3-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - Agenda, minutes and papers, 1971; F-2-3-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - Curriculum Committee Terms of Reference, 1972; F-2-3-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1972; F-2-3-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - Papers, 1972; F-2-3-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - New course proposals, 1972; F-2-3-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 2-24)
    - Minutes and papers, 1973; F-2-3-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 2-25)
    - Minutes and papers, 1974; F-2-3-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 2-25)
    - Minutes and papers, 1975; F-2-3-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 2-25)
    - Minutes and papers, 1976; F-2-3-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 2-25)
    - Minutes and papers, 1977; F-2-3-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 2-25)
    - Minutes and papers, 1978 - 1979; F-2-3-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 2-25)
  - Curriculum Committee, 1966 - 1978; F-2-3-3; 53 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Arts. Curriculum Committee
    - Terms of reference, F-2-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-25)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1966; F-2-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-25)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1967; F-2-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-25)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1968; F-2-3-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-25)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1969; F-2-3-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-26)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1970; F-2-3-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-26)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1970; F-2-3-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-26)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1971; F-2-3-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-26)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1971; F-2-3-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-26)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1972; F-2-3-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-26)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1972; F-2-3-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 2-26)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1973; F-2-3-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 2-26)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1973; F-2-3-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 2-26)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1974; F-2-3-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 2-27)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1975 - 1977; F-2-3-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 2-27)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1977 - 1978; F-2-3-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 2-27)
    - Committee Rulings, 1969 - 1971; F-2-3-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 2-27)
    - Papers, 1969; F-2-3-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 2-27)
    - Papers, 1970; F-2-3-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 2-27)
    - Papers, 1971; F-2-3-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 2-27)
    - Papers, 1971 - 1972; F-2-3-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 2-27)
    - Papers, 1972 - 1973; F-2-3-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 2-28)
    - Papers, 1973; F-2-3-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 2-28)
    - Papers, 1973 - 1974; F-2-3-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 2-28)
    - Papers, 1974 - 1975; F-2-3-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 2-28)
    - Memoranda, 1966 - 1969; F-2-3-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 2-28)
    - Memoranda, 1970 - 1971; F-2-3-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 2-28)
    - Memoranda, 1972 - 1973; F-2-3-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 2-28)
    - Memoranda, 1974; F-2-3-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 2-28)
    - Memoranda, 1975; F-2-3-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 2-28)
    - Memoranda, 1975; F-2-3-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 2-29)
    - Memoranda, 1976 - 1977; F-2-3-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 2-29)
    - Memoranda, F-2-3-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 2-29)
    - Memoranda, F-2-3-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 2-29)
    - Memoranda, F-2-3-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 2-29)
    - Memoranda, F-2-3-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 2-29)
  - Graduate Studies Committee, 1965 - 1978; F-2-3-4; 91 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Arts. Graduate Studies Committee
    - Terms of reference, F-2-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-29)
    - Regulations, F-2-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-29)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1965; F-2-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1965; F-2-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1966; F-2-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1966; F-2-3-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1967; F-2-3-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1967; F-2-3-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1968; F-2-3-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1968; F-2-3-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1969; F-2-3-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1969; F-2-3-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1970; F-2-3-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1970; F-2-3-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 2-30)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1970; F-2-3-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 2-31)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1970; F-2-3-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 2-31)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1970; F-2-3-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 2-31)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1971; F-2-3-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 2-31)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1972; F-2-3-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 2-31)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1973; F-2-3-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 2-31)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1973; F-2-3-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 2-31)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1973; F-2-3-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 2-31)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 2-32)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 2-32)
    - Papers and memoranda, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 2-32)
    - Papers A-C, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 2-32)
    - Papers D-H, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 2-32)
    - Papers I-L, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 2-32)
    - Papers M, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 2-32)
    - Papers N-P, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 2-32)
    - Papers Q-S, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 2-32)
    - Papers T-Z, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 2-33)
    - Papers, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 2-33)
    - Papers, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-34 (Archival box - standard 2-33)
    - Papers, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-35 (Archival box - standard 2-33)
    - Memoranda, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-36 (Archival box - standard 2-33)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1974; F-2-3-4-0-37 (Archival box - standard 2-33)
    - Papers A-C, 1975; F-2-3-4-0-38 (Archival box - standard 2-33)
    - Papers D-G, 1975; F-2-3-4-0-39 (Archival box - standard 2-33)
    - Papers H-M, 1975; F-2-3-4-0-40 (Archival box - standard 2-33)
    - Papers N-R, 1975; F-2-3-4-0-41 (Archival box - standard 2-34)
    - Papers S-Z, 1975; F-2-3-4-0-42 (Archival box - standard 2-34)
    - Papers, 1975; F-2-3-4-0-43 (Archival box - standard 2-34)
    - Papers, 1975; F-2-3-4-0-44 (Archival box - standard 2-34)
    - Papers, 1975; F-2-3-4-0-45 (Archival box - standard 2-34)
    - Papers, 1975; F-2-3-4-0-46 (Archival box - standard 2-34)
    - Memoranda, 1975; F-2-3-4-0-47 (Archival box - standard 2-34)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-48 (Archival box - standard 2-34)
    - Papers A-B, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-49 (Archival box - standard 2-34)
    - Papers C-E, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-50 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Papers F-H, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-51 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Papers J-L, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-52 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Papers M-N, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-53 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Papers O-T, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-54 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Papers U-Z, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-55 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Papers, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-56 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Papers, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-57 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Memoranda, 1976; F-2-3-4-0-58 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Agenda and minutes, 1977; F-2-3-4-0-59 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Papers A-B, 1977; F-2-3-4-0-60 (Archival box - standard 2-35)
    - Papers C-G, 1977; F-2-3-4-0-61 (Archival box - standard 2-36)
    - papers H-J, 1977; F-2-3-4-0-62 (Archival box - standard 2-36)
    - Papers K-M, 1977; F-2-3-4-0-63 (Archival box - standard 2-36)
    - Papers N-S, 1977; F-2-3-4-0-64 (Archival box - standard 2-36)
    - Papers T-Z, 1977; F-2-3-4-0-65 (Archival box - standard 2-36)
    - Papers, 1977; F-2-3-4-0-66 (Archival box - standard 2-36)
    - Memoranda, 1977; F-2-3-4-0-67 (Archival box - standard 2-36)
    - Papers, 1978; F-2-3-4-0-68 (Archival box - standard 2-36)
    - Papers, 1978; F-2-3-4-0-69 (Archival box - standard 2-36)
    - Memoranda, 1978; F-2-3-4-0-70 (Archival box - standard 2-36)
  - Tenure Committee, 1966 - 1978; F-2-3-5; 7 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Arts. Faculty Tenure Committee
    - Agenda, minutes, papers and memoranda, 1966; F-2-3-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers and memoranda, 1967; F-2-3-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers and memoranda, 1967; F-2-3-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers and memoranda, 1968; F-2-3-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers and memoranda, 1969 - 1978; F-2-3-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-37)
  - Undergraduate Curriculum Committee, 1968 - 1973; F-2-3-6; 1 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Arts. Undergraduate Curriculum Committee
    - Agenda and minutes, 1968 - 1973; F-2-3-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-37)
  - Departmental Review Committee, 1968 - 1975; F-2-3-7; 3 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Arts. Departmental Review Committee
    - Member Curriculum Vitae's, 1968; F-2-3-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-37)
    - Memoranda, 1974 - 1975; F-2-3-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-37)
  - Grading Committee, 1965 - 1977; F-2-3-8; 9 cm of textual records
    Faculty of Arts. Grading Committee
    - History outline and agenda and minutes, 1965 - 1967; F-2-3-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-37)
    - History outline and agenda and minutes, 1968 - 1971; F-2-3-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-38)
    - Memoranda, 1972 - 1976; F-2-3-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-38)
    - Grade distribution and practices within Faculty, 1971; F-2-3-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-38)
    - Grade Dispute, 1973; F-2-3-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-38)
    - President's Research Grant Committee, 1967; F-2-3-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-38)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971 - 1977; F-2-3-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-38)
  - Ad hoc committees, 1966 - 1979; F-2-3-9; 18 cm of textual records
    Sociology / Anthropology Articulation Committee; Faculty of Arts. Advisory Committee on Extension Credit Programs; Canada Council Small Grants Committee; Faculty of Arts Review Committee; Faculty of Arts. Departmental Assistants and Advisors Meeting; President's Committee on Research Involving Human Experimentation; Faculty of Arts. Committee on Interdisciplinary Studies; Faculty of Arts. Committee on Student Participation and Rights; Department of English. Ad Hoc Committee on Teaching Evaluation; Ad Hoc Assessment Committee for Graduate Program in Communication; Committee on Appointment of Heads; Faculty of Arts. Committee on Interdisplinary Courses; President's Advisory Committee on PSA Faculty
    - Articulation Committee, 1975; F-2-3-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 2-38)
    - Arts Advisory Committee, 1975; F-2-3-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 2-38)
    - Arts Review Committee, 1975; F-2-3-9-0-3 (Archival box - standard 2-38)
    - Canada Council Small Grants Committee Minutes, 1974 - 1978; F-2-3-9-0-4 (Archival box - standard 2-38)
    - Canada Council Small Grants Committee Minutes, 1978 - 1979; F-2-3-9-0-5 (Archival box - standard 2-39)
    - Department Assistants and Advisors minutes, 1972 - 1975; F-2-3-9-0-6 (Archival box - standard 2-39)
    - Research Ethics Committees, 1973 - 1976; F-2-3-9-0-7 (Archival box - standard 2-39)
    - Interdisciplinary Studies, 1968; F-2-3-9-0-8 (Archival box - standard 2-39)
    - Student Participation on Department Committees, 1969 - 1976; F-2-3-9-0-9 (Archival box - standard 2-39)
    - Teaching evaluation English Department, 1976; F-2-3-9-0-10 (Archival box - standard 2-39)
    - Assessment for Graduate Program in Communications, 1972; F-2-3-9-0-11 (Archival box - standard 2-39)
    - Committee on the Appointment of Heads, 1966 - 1967; F-2-3-9-0-12 (Archival box - standard 2-39)
    - Committee on Interdisciplinary Courses, 1967; F-2-3-9-0-13 (Archival box - standard 2-39)
    - President's Advisory Commitee on PSA faculty, 1975; F-2-3-9-0-14 (Archival box - standard 2-39)